radio.org.ph 2019-04-25

# Privacy policy | Radio.org.ph

This Privacy policy only concerns Radio.org.ph customers and users of our online services.  
Radio.org.ph works to ensure that your privacy is protected when using our services. We therefore have a policy setting out how your personal data will be processed and protected. Any changes we have made to this privacy policy can be found by visiting us online.

## How do we use your personal data?

In providing your personal details, you consent to us using the data collected in order to meet our commitments to you and to provide you with the service you expect. We will only keep your data for as long as necessary to carry out our services to you or for as long as we are required by law. After this your personal data will be deleted. We cannot remove your data when there is a legal storage requirement, such as book-keeping rules or when there are other legal grounds to keep the data, such as an ongoing contractual relationship.

## General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

In the European Economic Area (EEA) we only show you non-personalized ads. These ads are not based on your past behavior and do not use cookies for ad targeting.

## What are your rights?

You have the right to request information about the personal data we hold on you. If your data is incorrect, incomplete or irrelevant, you can ask to have the information corrected or removed. Annually, you have the right to request written documentation on the personal information we have about you in our account files. To request this document please write to Radio.org.ph Customer service. You can withdraw your consent to us using the data for marketing purposes (i.e. sending catalogues, newsletters or offers) at any time.

## Who has access to the data?

We never pass on, sell or swap your data to third parties for marketing purposes outside the Radio.org.ph Group.

## How do we protect your data?

We have taken technical and organisational measures to protect your data from loss, manipulation, unauthorised access, etc. We continually adapt our security measures in line with technological progress and developments. At Radio.org.ph we protect your data using encryption. Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) is a function that encrypts all information sent between buyer and seller.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is saved to, and, during subsequent visits, retrieved from your computer or mobile device. Radio.org.ph uses cookies to enhance and simplify your visit. We do not use cookies to store personal information or to disclose information to third parties.

There are two types of cookies: permanent and temporary (session cookies). Permanent cookies are stored as a file on your computer or mobile device for no longer than 12 months. Session cookies are stored temporarily and disappear when you close your browser session. We use permanent cookies to store your choice of start page and to store your details if you select “Remember me” when you log in.

You can easily erase cookies from your computer or mobile device using your browser. For instructions on how to handle and delete cookies please look under “Help” in your browser. You can choose to disable cookies or to receive a notification each time a new cookie is sent to your computer or mobile device. Please note that if you choose to disable cookies, you will not be able to take advantage of all our features.

## Third-party cookies

We use third-party cookies to collect statistics in aggregate form in analysis tools such as [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/policies/cookies/), [Google AdSense](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/), [Google Analytics](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/), [Google+](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/cookies/) and [Twitter](https://help.twitter.com/rules-and-policies/twitter-cookies). The cookies used are both permanent and temporary cookies (session cookies). The permanent cookies are stored on your computer or mobile device for no longer than 24 months.

## Links

Radio.org.ph may include links to other websites which do not fall under our supervision. We cannot accept any responsibility for the protection of privacy or the content of these websites, but we offer these links to make it easier for our visitors to find more information about specific subjects.

## Copyright

The content of this site is copyright-protected and is the property of Radio.org.ph.

## Third-party data processors

Radio.org.ph only uses third-party processors who are in compliance with the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and for every third-party processor a Data Processing Agreements (DPA) is in place.
